[
    {
      "Question": "1. What is 1 + 1?",
      "QuestionNumber": 1,
      "Answers": [1,2,3,4],
      "CorrectAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "Question": "2. What is 2 + 2?",
      "QuestionNumber": 2,
      "Answers": [1,5,3,4],
      "CorrectAnswer": 4
    },
    {
      "Question": "3. What is 3 + 3?",
      "QuestionNumber": 3,
      "Answers": [3,19,7,6],
      "CorrectAnswer": 6
    },
    {
      "Question": "4. What is 4 + 4?",
      "QuestionNumber": 4,
      "Answers": [8,1,16,3],
      "CorrectAnswer": 8
    },
    {
      "Question": "5.What is 5 + 5?",
      "QuestionNumber": 5,
      "Answers": [66,267,10,413],
      "CorrectAnswer": 10
    },
    {
      "Question": "6. What is 6 + 6?",
      "QuestionNumber": 6,
      "Answers": [12,135,993,444],
      "CorrectAnswer": 12
    },
    {
      "Question": "7. What is 7 + 7?",
      "QuestionNumber": 7,
      "Answers": [961,12,133,14],
      "CorrectAnswer": 14
    },
    {
      "Question": "8. What is 8 + 8?",
      "QuestionNumber": 8,
      "Answers": [111,16,31,88],
      "CorrectAnswer": 16
    },
    {
      "Question": "9. What is 9 + 9?",
      "QuestionNumber": 9,
      "Answers": [18,211,32,94],
      "CorrectAnswer": 18
    },
    {
      "Question": "10. What is 10 + 10?",
      "QuestionNumber": 10,
      "Answers": [12,51,20,41],
      "CorrectAnswer": 20
    }
]
